[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[crackling]
‐ This view's gonna be amazing.
I have a surprise for you.
‐ What's that?
‐ Close your eyes.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Open them.
‐ [laughs]
♪ ♪
Will you marry‐‐
‐ Yes.
[ominous music]
Where did you go?
This isn't funny. Todd.
Where are you?
[screams]
Help! Anyone!
Can you help?
[sobbing]
Please. help me!
Please.
Todd.
♪ ♪
[dramatic musical stings]
[woman screams]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[device blipping]
‐ All right.
That's the last one.
Please tell me
the mooring's intact.
‐ Looks fine.
The earthquake didn't cause
any visible cracks.
‐ All right. Great.
I get to stay
above water today.
Another chance for me to teach
your uncle how it's done.
‐ Whatever.
[laughs]
‐ Hey. Ray.
if you're not getting any bites.
let's pull it in.
Never want to stay
in the same spot too long.
‐ Hey. hey. hey. hey. hey. man.
What if this is the spot.
Hunter?
Come on. Slow and steady.
That's the McCray way.
‐ Maybe too slow and too steady
is the reason why
you still haven't caught
the big one. Uncle Ray.
‐ Yeah. Ray.
what about that big one?
‐ Hey. keep on.
Keep on.
I'm gonna show both of y'all.
Just keep on.
‐ We're gonna miss you.
Are you sure
you won't reconsider?
‐ Look around. Hunter.
[chuckles]
This?
This is heaven. baby.
You ain't gonna find anything
better than this.
‐ I'm not gonna pretend
I haven't become
fond of this place.
‐ And us?
‐ That's not the issue.
[fireworks popping. whistling]
[people cheering]
‐ What do they think
they're doing?
‐ Besides working
my last nerve?
I think they breaking
every maritime law there is.
‐ That's why some people
should stay on the shore.
‐ Yeah. they got fools
over there too. Hunter.
‐ That. my friend.
is why I live on a boat.
‐ I smell
a teachable moment coming.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Me too.
‐ ♪ Suck it ♪
♪ Do what I wanna do ♪
♪ Suck it ♪
♪ Live like I wanna live ♪
♪ And you can go to hell ♪
[Quint's "Suck It"]
‐ Whoo.
‐ [speaks foreign language]
♪ ♪
[boats thunk]
[laughter]
‐ Come on.
Move the clown car over here.
Move it. Move it.
[indistinct chatter. laughter]
[rock music playing over radio]
♪ ♪
‐ Who the hell are you?
‐ Adult supervision.
‐ Thanks. pops.
You know. I think we got it
from here. though.
‐ From here.
I don't see one person
that could pass
a field sobriety test.
‐ Harbor master. boy.
Hand over them fireworks.
‐ Do you have any idea
how much I spent on these?
‐ Not as much as you're gonna
have to pay the tourist police
if I turn you in.
‐ Whatever.
Have fun.
[grunts]
[bottles clinking]
♪ ♪
‐ I took this off him.
Get your boat fixed.
‐ See?
He's cool.
Cheers to Mr. Tik.
‐ [speaks foreign language]
[bottles clink]
[birds chirping]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
‐ You see the look
on the kid's face
when you took his fireworks?
‐ [laughs]
‐ Priceless.
‐ You better grab that pole.
Ray. before it's gone.
‐ Oh. shi‐‐
Come on.
[rod clicking]
Ooh. I got it. It's the big one!
I got it. I got it this time.
‐ Come on.
‐ Almost. almost. almost.
‐ Easy.
‐ Come on. Here's a big one.
‐ I got it! I got it!
[rod thunks]
♪ ♪
‐ What's that?
[all groan]
‐ Fires?
Dead bodies?
I'm gonna have to start taking
my blood pressure medicine
before I leave the dock.
‐ He's been in the water
a long time.
[device blipping]
‐ You guys need to look at this.
Maybe that's where
the body came from.
‐ That's not good.
I'm gonna call the authorities.
Let's head in.
‐ I'm gonna pull the drone.
‐ I'ma cover his ugly ass up.
♪ ♪
[shudders]
Could this be an algae bloom?
‐ Yeah. maybe if we were
in the Caribbean.
Not in these waters. though.
‐ Uncle Ray?
‐ [shrieks]
‐ [screams]
[screaming]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Get off my niece!
Hell is wrong with you. man?
Look. stay right there
where you at.
Look. you don't want
none of this. man.
I don't know who you are
or what you are.
but you better
stay the hell away from me.
‐ [shaky breathing]
‐ I don't know about you.
You want some of this?
‐ I'm scared.
Get back.
Come on.
Hunter!
‐ [sobbing]
‐ Stay right here.
‐ Please.
‐ Oh. stop. man.
Look. I said stop!
You know what "halt" means?
Man. you better move.
I'm not playing with you.
‐ Ray. take care of Jada.
I got this.
♪ ♪
Look. buddy.
I don't know
what you've been through.
but unless you back off.
this is gonna
go through you next.
‐ Jada!
Oh. no.
Baby. please.
Shh.
♪ ♪
Shh. it's okay.
‐ I'm scared.
Shh. stay right here.
Shh.
Stay with me. baby.
Stay.
‐ Is she all right?
‐ Is it dead?
Is it go‐‐is it gone?
‐ Did you kill it?
‐ I think so.
‐ Good.
[ominous music]
Hunter!
‐ Oh. you've got
to be kidding me.
‐ It's just a meth head. right?
Some old punk washed up
on the side of the pier.
‐ [snarls]
‐ [shouts]
‐ I don't know. Ray. why don't
you show him your badge?
Maybe that'll stop him.
‐ Formalities ended
when he bit my niece!
‐ [snarling]
Got to be a rational
explanation. right?
‐ Well. if you got one.
I'm all ears.
[grunts]
Buh‐bye.
[panting]
‐ You want some more of this?
You better not
come back over here.
‐ Ray?
‐ Oh. shit.
Jada.
Shh.
It's okay.
Shh. shh.
Are we dreaming?
‐ No.
I wish we were.
‐ Shh.
I got this. man.
Go radio for help. please.
‐ I'm on it.
‐ Stay with me.
Shh.
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[laughter]
‐ So this makes. what.
five double shifts in a row now?
‐ Six. if you're counting.
‐ [sighs] Mom. when's the
last time you had a date?
Look. she's hot. right. Taani?
‐ Smokin'.
‐ You're sweet.
What I do is more important
than how I look.
‐ But you just need
to find some balance.
Dad's been gone a long time.
He'd want you to be happy.
‐ I am happy.
[phone buzzing]
‐ Now that's more like it.
‐ Hello?
‐ I've got an accident
on my hands here.
‐ Let me guess.
Another charter client
cast his line
into his buddy's tackle box?
‐ No. but I owe you
dinner for that.
‐ And a bottle of wine.
The trauma still lingers.
‐ It's a different
kind of accident.
It's Ray's niece.
She's hurt pretty bad.
‐ Uh. yeah.
I'm on my way.
Duty calls.
‐ More like booty calls.
‐ What'd he say?
‐ Enough.
‐ Look. all I'm saying is
what's the point
of living in paradise without
someone to share it with?
‐ When I get home.
you better be there.
walls still standing.
‐ Promise.
I love you.
‐ I'll take care of her.
Mrs. Wright.
‐ Yeah.
That's what I'm afraid of.
‐ [laughs]
‐ Bye.
[indistinct chatter]
[engine whirs]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Come on.
Give me your arm.
I got you.
Wasn't nothing normal
about that back there. Hunter.
I mean. nothing we did
was even able to stop him.
How do we know
there's no more out there
looking for another
midday snack. huh?
‐ Hey. Ray. reel it in.
Reel it in.
♪ ♪
‐ [groans]
‐ You're gonna be okay.
‐ Okay.
‐ Hey. guys.
‐ Hey. Doc.
‐ Hey. Jada?
‐ What happened?
‐ Curved laceration.
Tissue loss.
This is a bite wound.
What happened?
‐ Look. we pulled this dead guy
in off the water. right?
We laid him down and then...
[gobbles]
His teeth‐‐
he started biting everybody.
and then Hunter grabbed
a machete. and he went‐‐
‐ Hey. hey. hey.
This guy regains consciousness.
he starts biting
and attacking everybody.
and then
we throw him overboard.
‐ It's okay. Jada.
You're okay. honey.
‐ Okay.
Coming through.
‐ So are you gonna be leaving?
‐ Yeah. tomorrow's
my last day in Emrys Bay.
‐ No good‐byes?
You owe me dinner.
[siren whoops]
‐ You'll be okay.
‐ Are you coming or not?
‐ I'm gonna talk
to Sheriff Akoni.
see if we can figure out
what's going on out there.
‐ Truck's in the lot.
Meet us at the hospital later?
‐ Got it.
[door thunks]
[engine turns over]
[sirens wailing]
Hey.
Thanks for getting here
so quick.
‐ No problem.
‐ She's really gonna be okay.
right?
‐ She's gonna be fine.
[seagulls cawing]
‐ [clears throat]
‐ This is Akoni.
I'm at the pier.
The water looks calm.
It's all fine here.
‐ Head out
to Comet's Beach next.
‐ Copy that.
Thought you'd be long gone.
Shaw.
‐ Yeah. well.
sometimes the heart and head
aren't always in sync.
‐ Is there a reason why you're
walking around with a machete?
‐ Uh. if you saw what I saw.
you'd want one in both hands.
‐ Yeah. Ray called in.
Some kind of sea monster?
‐ A lunatic attacked his niece.
‐ Beach squatter?
Boating accident? What?
‐ I've been working
on the water for 30 years.
I have never. ever.
seen anything like this.
‐ I don't have the time to go
on a wild goose chase with you.
‐ What's going on out there
is a bigger problem.
You see that. right?
‐ [sighs]
Okay.
‐ Come on.
Take a ride with me.
["Party (To Raise the Dead)"
playing]
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ You hear the sounds
that come in waves ♪
‐ The singer's name is Dag.
Or maybe you're
into the drummer.
His name is Ivan.
He's Russian!
[laughs]
Interested?
‐ Ask me again when
I can hear myself think.
‐ Yeah. party!
♪ Party. party. party ♪
♪ Today's the day we party ♪
♪ Party. party ♪
♪ Today's the day ♪
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
‐ Chemical spill?
‐ Maybe.
‐ That's the only thing
I could think of
that may explain that guy
we saw on the boat today.
‐ Where's the body?
‐ I don't know.
This is where we threw it
overboard. though.
‐ We need to see where
the source is coming from.
‐ I got eyes for you.
‐ Rand. you're so cool.
Muah. muah. muah.
That was incredible.
‐ I know.
‐ So you like our set?
‐ Yeah. You guys were...
[laughs]
‐ Not your kind of thing. huh?
‐ No. we had fun.
Just doesn't really
seem like you.
‐ Thank you.
Rand's taste is more
"mallet to the head."
Me?
All I want is fans
who like our music because
it comes from the heart.
not because it's loud.
[laughs]
I'm Dag.
‐ Sam.
[laughs]
‐ I think the earthquake may
have something to do with this.
[tense music]
[device blipping]
♪ ♪
We didn't go this deep
last time.
Is that a documented wreck?
‐ Not that I'm aware of.
‐ Ship's name and designation
have been removed.
‐ No telling where
it's from then.
‐ No. this is an Anton 350 made
by Anders Marine in Denmark.
Very few were ever made with
this extended 80‐foot hull.
Whatever took it down
took down a very rare ship.
‐ How do you know that?
‐ Grew up in San Pedro.
right off the docks.
Some people know cars.
I know boats.
♪ ♪
‐ There's the light source.
[ominous music]
Did you see that?
‐ Yeah. um.
I put a machete into the chest
of one of these guys today.
It didn't stop him‐‐
didn't slow him down one bit.
‐ Come on. Shaw.
‐ Tell you what
I think they are.
‐ What's that?
‐ It's alive. but dead.
‐ Let's stick to reality.
♪ ♪
‐ These are zombies.
‐ [laughs]
You got me. Shaw.
You got me.
♪ ♪
[zombies snarling]
Don't even say it.
Get us out of here.
Pok. there's been some kind
of outbreak offshore.
Evac is mandatory.
Get everyone off the beach now.
and find my daughter.
‐ Attention:
by order
of the Emrys Bay Police.
the beach is closed.
This is a mandatory evacuation
until further notice.
This is not a drill.
[phone buzzing]
[phone beeps]
‐ Hey.
‐ Hey. Doc.
Akoni and I think there's
been some kind of outbreak.
so isolate Jada.
keep your eyes open
for anyone else who comes in
with similar injuries.
‐ Okay.
What are we talking about here?
‐ Danny. check this out.
‐ Clear the beach.
Seek shelter.
[foreboding music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[alarm blaring]
[indistinct shouting]
‐ Could you...
[inaudible]
It should be over there.
‐ Uh. that's not a sound
I like to hear.
‐ Look. Sam's at my house
with Akoni's daughter.
If anything happens.
can you get to them?
‐ Got it. but the tsunami's
only part of the problem.
There's been
some kind of outbreak.
‐ I've got to start
prepping patients for evac.
You be safe.
‐ Wait. wait.
Wait!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What are we gonna do
about those things?
‐ What are you gonna
do about that?
♪ ♪
‐ Oh. my gosh‐‐a tsunami.
‐ That's totally insane.
‐ Your mom's gonna have
a busy shift.
‐ Your dad too.
‐ So I guess
we're not getting tacos.
♪ ♪
‐ Where do you
think you're going?
We need to get behind the wave.
‐ I've seen those things.
I know what they're capable of.
When the wave hits the beach.
flooding's gonna be
the least of our problems.
People are gonna need our help.
‐ How are we gonna do that
without getting
ourselves killed?
‐ We're gonna ride
the barrel of the wave.
When we get to the beach.
we'll storm it.
We'll help everybody
that we can.
‐ You know you're crazy. right?
‐ Hang on.
[engine revs]
♪ ♪
[people shouting.
cars honking]
♪ ♪
[zombies snarling]
It's a zombie tsunami.
Come on.
They're moving past us.
[boat creaking]
[people shouting]
[zombie snarls]
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
[zombies snarling]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[gun clicks]
‐ Save your bullets.
‐ [snarling]
‐ [gagging]
[coughing]
‐ Blaine?
Blaine. honey. are you okay?
‐ [panting]
‐ Shaun didn't make it.
‐ But we did. baby.
That's all that matters.
Hey!
What'd I say?
Baby!
Hey. look. if there was ever
a time to celebrate. this is it.
[monitor beeping]
‐ Okay. so we'll only
keep you two isolated
until we know everything's okay.
‐ Great.
It keeps getting
better and better.
‐ It's just a precaution until
we can determine
what this outbreak is.
‐ What I saw out there‐‐
it's gonna take more than this
to kill them.
‐ Dr. Wright.
we need you outside.
‐ Okay.
Hang in there.
I'll check in soon.
but I got to get back.
This evacuation's reduced us
to a skeleton staff.
[ominous music]
[indistinct chatter]
‐ I'm trying.
No!
‐ Come on.
they're not breathing!
What's wrong?
♪ ♪
‐ You took one of them on?
‐ Yeah. Ray and I.
It was a lot easier when
we could throw them overboard.
‐ Hey!
Hey. get away from them!
Get off the beach!
‐ They're hurt.
They need help.
‐ Come on!
Come on!
[zombies snarling]
‐ Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
‐ [grunting]
‐ [screams]
[people shouting]
‐ [screaming]
‐ [shrieks]
‐ You see what
I'm talking about here?
‐ [snarling]
‐ Zombies it is.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ I still can't get a hold
of my mom or‐‐or anybody.
What about your dad?
‐ No. nothing yet.
[people screaming]
[zombies snarling]
‐ What's wrong
with their faces?
‐ Tsunami must have
messed them up.
‐ What if those things
get up here?
‐ We've got to get away
from this place.
Come on.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Come on. this way.
Let's go.
‐ [screaming]
‐ I'll take care of that one.
‐ Watch out.
Watch out.
‐ Get out of here.
[gunshot]
‐ [snarls]
‐ Out of my way.
[suspenseful music]
[grunting]
‐ Get out. Get out.
‐ Run. run. come on!
‐ [grunts]
[engine whirring]
♪ ♪
‐ Run!
‐ Let's get out of here.
Thank you!
[monitor beeping]
‐ Uncle Ray.
‐ Hey. baby.
‐ I'm so cold.
‐ Oh. it's gonna be okay.
Let me get you some cover.
‐ So hungry. I just...
[retches]
‐ Shh.
That's‐‐shh. shh.
Let me get the nurse to bring
you something to eat. okay?
[monitor beeping rapidly]
Jada?
[monitor blipping. blaring]
Jada!
‐ [huffs]
‐ Hey. hey. stay with me.
Jada. stay with me.
No. no.
No. Jada.
Jada. what you doing?
[dramatic music]
[screaming]
Hey. hey. stop!
Hey!
Jada. stop!
What you doing?
‐ [snarling]
‐ [grunting]
♪ ♪
‐ Jada. get off him!
Stop doing that!
‐ [screams]
‐ No!
Hey. help!
Help!
‐ Beach is overrun.
‐ We've got to set up a triage
for the victims.
‐ [snarling]
[zombies snarling]
Maybe not.
‐ Let's get back to the station.
regroup. and call for backup.
‐ Ray's truck.
♪ ♪
[screaming]
‐ They're everywhere!
[people shouting]
‐ [screams]
‐ [indistinct]
‐ Stop!
Stop. stop.
Don't shoot.
‐ Man. we're not one of them.
‐ [panting]
You again.
‐ [sighs]
Yeah. of course.
[panting]
[exhales]
I see you got a new sidekick.
‐ I'm sorry.
He's an idiot.
Can you please help us?
‐ Where'd you two come from?
‐ We were at the beach.
It was‐‐it was awful.
and we lost Shaun.
‐ Could you just. like.
get us to our hotel
or something?
‐ Five‐star hotel's not gonna
protect you from that.
‐ What's that even
supposed to mean?
‐ That it's not a problem
you can buy your way out of.
[woman screams]
‐ So buckle up. sweetheart.
[gun clicks]
They're coming.
[engine turns over]
[tires screech]
[birds chirping]
♪ ♪
[elevator dings]
‐ [sighs]
[muttering]
4. 5. 0. 8.
[soft chewing sounds]
Hello?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
‐ [snarls]
‐ [screams]
[dramatic music]
Someone. help!
Somebody!
[grunting]
No!
Oh. my God.
Have you seen what's out there?
‐ Yeah.
‐ [Jada snarling]
‐ If the contagion's aerosol.
you could contract it
from breathing.
‐ Unless you plan on
tying their mouths shut.
this is not gonna get it.
‐ They're infected.
Clearly. it's a contagion.
‐ Look. it's more than that!
They rode in here
on that big‐ass wave.
bringing a double dose
of disaster to this town
like nobody's seen.
so I suggest you lace up
your running shoes. Doc.
because if what's
out there bites you.
it's game over.
‐ How‐‐how is this happening?
‐ How?
Why?
I stopped caring about that
when I saw my niece
bite the head off
of that orderly.
Do you know
what that sounds like?
what that looks like?
‐ Ugh.
[banging on door]
Move right to acceptance. Doc.
'cause denial
is a death sentence.
[tapping on door]
[zombies snarling]
[tires screech]
‐ I can't reach
any other units on comms.
Has anyone reported in?
‐ No one.
‐ What are we dealing
with here. sir?
‐ Welcome to Crazy Town.
Officer Pok.
♪ ♪
‐ Come on.
Come on!
‐ Blaine. come on.
‐ [shouts]
‐ [screams]
‐ Get up!
Come on!
‐ Sorry.
‐ Blaine!
[screaming]
[flesh squelching]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
‐ Give me the chair!
‐ [grunts]
‐ [snarling]
‐ Get me the other one.
Come on. Doc.
[grunts]
We can't stop them
all with just these.
‐ I know.
Okay.
We cut through the terrace.
The admin offices
are right next door.
[door rattling]
‐ [snarling]
‐ Terrace it is.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ How could you do that?
‐ Man. it's everybody
for themselves!
‐ She saved your ass.
‐ What would you expect me
to do. man. huh?
Let them bite me?
[thunking on windows]
No way.
I'm gonna do everything
it takes to survive.
Including this.
Lower your weapon.
Lower your weapon!
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Put it down.
‐ You got some balls. kid.
‐ I got bullets too.
‐ Take it easy.
‐ I want those
big guns in there.
‐ That's not gonna happen.
‐ Give me the keys now!
Open the door!
Give me the keys!
Open the door.
Give me the keys now.
Now!
[grunts]
[somber music]
‐ Stay with me. Pok.
Stay with me.
♪ ♪
This kid's worse
than the things outside.
‐ Rand!
‐ [grunts]
No time for "pay to play."
‐ Let's go!
‐ Come on.
This way.
[people shouting indistinctly]
[dramatic music]
[flesh squelching]
♪ ♪
‐ Hey. hey. wait. wait. wait.
‐ [shouts]
Check out here.
Go. go. go. go.
‐ [yelps]
‐ Oh.
‐ Come on.
Come on.
‐ I think I sprained my ankle.
‐ Okay.
Okay. duck.
Duck.
[tense music]
[zombies snarling softly]
♪ ♪
‐ [screams]
‐ Oh. my God!
‐ Taani! [screams]
Help. help. help!
‐ [screams]
‐ [snarls]
‐ Taani!
Come on. Ta...
[grunts]
‐ [shrieks]
‐ [screams]
‐ [screaming]
[flesh squelching]
‐ Taani. look out!
‐ Get away from them!
‐ Go! Go!
We'll find you!
‐ Okay.
Okay.
♪ ♪
[zombies snarling]
[radio static]
‐ This is Emrys Bay station
issuing an open‐channel mayday.
In addition to tsunami damage.
we've had an outbreak
of unknown origin.
Over.
[soft dramatic music]
To all naval assets
in the vicinity.
this is Emrys Bay station
issuing an open‐channel mayday.
[mic thunks]
[keypad beeps]
[shredder whirring]
Tell me again why
I didn't shoot that kid dead.
‐ That thing
hanging around your neck.
‐ Fair enough.
‐ So I logged into the maritime
registry using Ray's account.
There's only one Anton 350
in the regional archives.
and it's registered to Revok
Industries from 1981 to 1985.
but then it was decommissioned.
Status now is salvaged. junked.
‐ Then what's it doing
at the bottom of the ocean?
‐ Exactly.
Something doesn't add up.
[door rattles]
‐ I think we've got
more pressing issues.
‐ The key to all this
is this ship.
If we can find one person
that knows something about it.
maybe we can get some answers.
[glass shattering]
‐ It's not safe here.
We got to go.
‐ We're gonna need
some more firepower.
[glass clattering]
‐ Okay. we cross over
to the main building.
We cut through Radiology.
‐ Okay.
[tense musical sting]
‐ Oh. hell no!
‐ [snarling]
‐ Bite me.
Jada. don't you have
something else to do?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Oh. my God.
Whatever that is.
it's not Jada.
‐ Yeah. I know.
Still not gonna be an easy call
to my sister Gina. though.
Mm‐mm.
‐ [snarling]
[door rattles]
‐ We pulled enough hardware
off drug boats and narco planes
over the years
to outfit a small army.
‐ Wow.
Did you get this off
a drug dealer?
‐ Some kid bought it online
with his mom's credit card.
Went all shogun
on his brother's bedroom.
‐ What happened to his brother?
‐ Still looking
for his pinky toe.
‐ [panting]
‐ When we're done with them.
we're gonna find my daughter.
‐ Hey!
Hey...
[groans]
Dude. are you serious right now?
Seriously. you guys can't
just leave me like this.
‐ Let's go kill some dead guys.
‐ Hey!
Hey. this is murder!
Hey!
‐ [grunts]
‐ I can't hold them off
any longer.
[shouts]
Do it now!
[flesh plopping]
Nice job.
[zombies grunting]
‐ They're still squirming.
‐ I'll take squirming
over biting any day.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[zombies snarling]
‐ Reinforcements.
[waves crashing]
‐ 'Cause one would
have been too easy.
‐ Come on.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[engine turns over]
You shoot a zombie in the head.
they're supposed to die. right?
‐ Maybe there's
something more.
‐ That's what I'm afraid of.
[tires screech]
[birds ♪ ♪rping]
‐ [panting]
[yelps]
‐ Look.
Dead ahead.
‐ They're getting on my nerves.
Hold on.
♪ ♪
Roadkill.
‐ [snarls]
‐ [snarling]
‐ [panting]
[tense music]
Come on.
♪ ♪
Don't look back.
Come on.
Come on. be quick.
[rock music playing
through headphones]
Wake up!
Come on. open the door!
Wake up! Wake up!
‐ Come on!
They're trying to kill us!
‐ What's going on. man?
What's wrong with them?
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Get back in here. Ivan.
‐ Rock and roll. baby!
[grunting]
‐ Come on!
We gotta go!
We got to go now!
‐ [screams]
[engine sputtering]
Car's dead.
What are we gonna do?
‐ We'll figure this out.
‐ They're everywhere.
[flesh squelching]
‐ [panting]
[monitor beeping]
♪ ♪
[gate rattles]
Come on!
[grunts]
Hello?
‐ This is private property.
The gate's there for a reason.
so just go away.
‐ No. no.
No.
I need your help. please.
They're after me.
‐ Turn around.
I need to check you out.
‐ Look. perv.
just open the door!
‐ Have you been bitten?
‐ What?
Look.
Look at me.
Do I look like
I have been bitten?
‐ Show me the back
of your head.
‐ Oh. my God!
Fine.
If you don't open the door now.
I am gonna be bit.
Are we all good?
[door buzzes]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[chains rattle]
‐ [snarling]
♪ ♪
Hello?
[panting]
Yeah. yeah. okay.
You live here by yourself?
‐ Yeah.
‐ That explains
the Unabomber chic.
[Taser fizzing]
Can you please put that away?
‐ You first.
‐ Okay.
‐ I've been watching
from up here.
Looks really bad.
I have monitors all around town.
When these things arrived.
just about everyone was infected
in less than an hour.
‐ There are so many of them.
I need to call my dad.
Can I‐‐can I use that?
Please?
Thank you.
Dad. do you copy?
‐ Taani. where are you?
You're okay?
You don't know how glad I am
to hear your voice.
‐ Yeah.
I'm safe.
I'm. uh...
I'm at the compound
on top of the hillside.
‐ At Driscoll's?
I told you never
to go near that place.
He's crazy.
‐ Yeah.
Great.
Dad. I didn't really
have a choice. 'kay?
His place is pretty fortified.
Do you really want me to leave?
‐ No.
I don't want you to leave.
‐ I need you to go get Sam.
We got separated at the market.
‐ Just stay put.
We'll come to you.
‐ Be careful.
‐ Stay safe.
♪ ♪
‐ At least we know she's okay.
‐ [softly]
Yeah.
[gate rattling.
zombies snarling]
‐ We should. uh.
probably go in now.
‐ Yeah.
[foreboding musical sting]
‐ [grunting]
[door clicks]
[sighs]
So long. sucker.
[dramatic musical sting]
‐ [snarls]
‐ Hey. baby.
Hey.
Baby...
[stammers] I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean anything
by that. baby.
[grunts]
[screaming]
‐ You have to find a way out.
‐ No. you're coming with me.
‐ I can't. I'll slow you down.
‐ No. I'm not leaving you.
‐ You're gonna have to.
You'll move faster without me.
‐ Yeah. well.
what are you gonna do?
‐ I'm gonna get their attention.
[zombies snarling]
‐ [grunting]
‐ Wait. here.
Take this.
‐ [shouts]
Right here!
Over here!
["Party (To Raise the Dead)"
acoustic version playing]
♪ You hear the sounds
that come in waves ♪
[tires screeching]
♪ By people dancing
on a grave ♪
‐ Here! Help!
Over here! Help. help!
‐ ♪ And things are just about
to get depraved ♪
♪ We'll party ♪
‐ [snarls]
‐ ♪ Party. party ♪
♪ Party to raise the dead ♪
[gunshot]
♪ Party. party ♪
‐ Come on.
‐ [screams]
‐ ♪ Party ♪
♪ To raise the dead ♪
[gunshot]
♪ 'Cause once
you're underground ♪
[gunshot]
♪ You won't hear a sound ♪
‐ We got to go get him.
He‐‐he hurt his foot.
‐ We'll get him.
‐ [shrieks]
‐ [screaming]
[flesh squelching]
‐ Come on.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[somber music]
‐ Hey. Sam.
It's gonna be all right.
‐ He's dead because of me.
I‐I don't know where
my mom is. and‐‐
and we got separated from Taani.
‐ Taani's gonna be fine.
She's the one who told us
where to find you.
‐ They didn't get her?
‐ No.
We're gonna get your mom
at the hospital.
and then we're gonna get Taani.
Don't you worry.
‐ Thank you. Hunter.
[tires screech]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Let's be quick. Shaw.
‐ I'm on it.
See if you can text your mom.
‐ Still no signal.
‐ She could be anywhere.
‐ I need to let her know
that I'm here.
‐ Anything we do is gonna
draw their attention.
‐ Exactly.
I need to get
to the nurse's station.
‐ Well. you're not going alone.
‐ I know every inch
of this place.
You two will just slow me down.
[door rattling]
‐ Take this. You're gonna
need to protect yourself.
‐ I know how to use a gun.
‐ You're not getting a gun.
‐ Fine.
♪ ♪
[door creaks]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[door thunks]
Awesome.
Coast is clear.
[exhales]
‐ Wait!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [snarls]
‐ The patients
are getting restless.
‐ [snarls]
‐ Time for their medicine.
[gun clicks]
[lock clicks]
♪ ♪
[pleasant tone over speakers]
‐ Attention. please.
‐ What's she doing?
‐ I don't know.
‐ This is an important message
for Dr. Kenzie Wright.
Please come to the second floor
of the nurse's station
to claim your daughter.
She's extremely worried.
and would like to leave
this freak show behind.
‐ [snarling]
♪ ♪
‐ Can't hold them off
for much longer.
‐ I don't know what's worse‐‐
their teeth...
[grunts]
Or their breath.
‐ [yelps]
‐ [grunts]
Got any ideas?
‐ Let's see if we can shock
some sense into them.
[electricity crackles]
‐ [screaming]
[frantic music]
[electricity crackles]
‐ [grunts]
‐ Let go!
Let go!
Please!
[screams]
[panting]
‐ [snarling]
♪ ♪
[shouts]
[zombies grunting]
[elevator dings]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
‐ Hey.
Sam's safe.
‐ Is she on this floor?
‐ Down the hall.
‐ Ray. take this.
[broom clatters]
‐ You two guys been having
a cookout?
‐ Just go.
[foreboding music]
‐ Sam?
Sam. come on.
[intense musical sting]
[grunts]
Sam?
‐ Mom!
‐ [sobs]
‐ Come on.
Grab her hands.
I'll get her feet.
‐ [snarling]
Get your knife.
‐ You're okay.
‐ Come on.
Let's go.
‐ All right.
[zombie snarling]
‐ Wait. Hang on.
These‐‐these ones are different.
‐ Yeah. this is one of the ones
that started all this.
He came in on the waves.
‐ It looks like these guys
were experimented on.
[door rattling]
‐ We got to get out.
‐ Sam. Kenzie. stay by me.
Come on.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ All right. get in the car.
[tires screeching]
♪ ♪
‐ Go easy on Driscoll.
He doesn't like guests.
[zombies snarling]
[device beeping.
door buzzing]
‐ Dad!
‐ You said you weren't
going out.
Now this time.
you put your friend in danger.
‐ I know.
I'm sorry.
‐ It's okay.
It's okay.
‐ Oh. my gosh.
Are you all right?
‐ Have you been bitten?
‐ No. I haven't been.
‐ No! No! No!
No biters in the house.
‐ I said I wasn't bitten.
[foreboding music]
[door rattles]
Shaw.
‐ Hey. before we bail.
do you mind if we use
that radio to call for help?
‐ Just don't mess up
anything on my desk.
‐ [scoffs]
[radio static]
‐ This is Officer Kameo Akoni
of Emrys Bay.
We need assistance.
Anyone out there?
‐ [snarls]
‐ It's quiet out there.
Cell towers are down.
There hasn't been any chatter
on the radio for hours.
Not that I'd want
to talk to anybody.
‐ We've had two tsunamis.
and no one has come
to check on us in town.
‐ Well. that should tell you
something right there.
‐ Help has to be on the way.
‐ Coast Guard's coming.
‐ There's no one out there.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
‐ [grunting]
[screams]
[loud thunk]
‐ Akoni?
‐ What's going on down there?
‐ Akoni!
‐ Dad?
‐ Run!
It's coming!
‐ Akoni!
‐ Dad!
‐ What the hell
is going on down there?
Say something!
Akoni!
‐ Stay back. Sam.
‐ Akoni!
‐ [gasps]
‐ [snarls]
‐ [grunts]
‐ Mom!
[Taser crackling]
‐ [shouting]
‐ Thanks. Driscoll.
[Taser buzzes]
‐ No problem.
‐ Way to go. Mom.
‐ Everybody okay?
‐ [gasps]
Dad?
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ [sobbing indistinctly]
‐ I'm sorry. baby.
‐ No.
‐ I'm so sorry.
‐ No!
‐ I'm sorry.
[somber music]
‐ No.
‐ We can't stay here.
‐ Place held up just fine
till you whackadoodles
showed up.
‐ Oh. your little
science project
that almost killed
my daughter and I?
We can agree
that one's on you. right?
‐ And exactly
what were you doing
with your bunkmate down there?
‐ Trying to figure out
what makes them tick.
‐ What'd you learn?
‐ The liquid inside it tested
consistent with phosphorus.
‐ That explains
the blue glow in the water.
‐ The Taser is the only thing
I've seen that could stop it.
‐ We stopped a whole bunch
in the hospital
with electricity as well.
That's why I connected
the Taser to the sword.
[sword crackles]
‐ [laughs]
‐ Zombie nuts roasting
on a open fire.
‐ How are gonna kill them all
with one Taser?
‐ Downed power lines.
I saw several of them
at the beach.
but the grid is still running.
We use the tidal pools
to conduct the electricity.
All we need to do is lure
the zombies into the water.
and then we run the power to it.
‐ Fish in a barrel.
‐ But the ship is not
in your barrel.
‐ We're gonna have
to blow up that ship too.
If we can take care
of most of them.
then the Coast Guard
can take care
of the stragglers
when they get here.
‐ If they get here.
‐ Okay.
How do we blow up the ship?
‐ Here.
Ta‐da.
You can take this C4 with you.
You can take grenades.
You can even take this cereal
with you when you leave.
You're gonna leave. right?
‐ I'll take the ones on land.
‐ I guess I'm the captain
of the boat. huh?
What the hell
do I know about C4?
‐ Driscoll. we're gonna need
your help with that.
A lot of people are gonna die
unless we stop them.
‐ [sighs softly]
All right.
I'm in.
‐ I'll clear a path.
and we'll all make a run for it.
[zombies snarling]
[Quint's "Meat Machine"]
♪ ♪
[sword crackles]
[sword fizzes]
Oh...
[button clicking]
Come on.
♪ ♪
‐ What's wrong?
‐ His Taser isn't working.
He needs my help.
♪ ♪
‐ Come on.
Fire up the wood chipper.
It's feeding time.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Trick or treat ♪
♪ Mind your teeth ♪
♪ For him.
every day is Halloween ♪
♪ ♪
‐ [grunts]
[wood chipper whirring.
flesh squelching]
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ If you play his game ♪
♪ He's got a wing
in the bad guy's house ♪
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Meat machine ♪
♪ Meat machine ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Meat. meat ♪
♪ Meat machine ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Meat. meat ♪
♪ Meat machine ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Nice moves.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Come on. Driscoll!
Come on. let's go!
You're gonna have
some good roses this year.
‐ Yeah. yeah. yeah.
‐ Come on. Let's go.
‐ No. you come on.
Let's go.
‐ Hurry up.
It's over here.
‐ Hey. hey. wait a minute. man!
Wait!
‐ [softly] ‐ All right.
Hey. hey. hey. your step.
Look.
if anything happens to me.
just take care of Sam. okay?
‐ Nothing's gonna happen
to either of you.
I promise.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Should have just
followed my instincts‐‐
motored to another port
where it's safe.
‐ So that's why
you live in a boat?
So you can take off
when things get rough?
‐ [sighs]
‐ I always knew you weren't
the settling‐down
type of guy. Hunter.
Knowing that made it easier
to be friends
without getting hurt.
‐ Seeing you and Sam
at the hospital.
risking everything
to get back to each other‐‐
Taani and her dad
doing the same thing.
I thought I had it all.
Made me realize
I don't have anything.
‐ Aw. hell no.
Look. y'all been beating
around the bush for months.
This ain't no time
for canoodling.
[indistinct chatter]
‐ [coughing]
‐ Sam!
Sam!
‐ Come on.
‐ Shh. shh. shh. shh.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Yeah.
‐ We both know how this
is going to end.
‐ It's not over till it's over.
‐ Doesn't anyone else
think it's weird
that he ain't turned yet?
‐ They didn't bite
through his head
and penetrate his skull‐‐
didn't get to the brain.
I've been watching
on my monitors.
It takes longer
through the skin.
‐ Town's in your hands now.
Hunter.
Take care of it.
And take care of them.
Do it better than I did.
‐ What's that supposed to mean?
‐ [sighs]
I'll tell you what I know.
Revok Pharmaceuticals
came here 30 years ago.
They claimed to be
making major strides
with a new antiaging drug.
They needed to test it
on humans.
away from FDA scrutiny
in the United States.
They brought in staff.
patients. security.
and the local council leaders
and I just needed to make sure
that everything
stayed off the radar.
[sighs]
They paid us.
They financed trips.
and they made sure that my wife
got the best medical treatment
before she passed on.
‐ If you wouldn't mind
fast‐forwarding to the part
where the zombies come to town.
I think we'd all appreciate it.
‐ They lied.
The drug wasn't ready.
They shouldn't have been
trying it on humans.
There are hideous side effects.
and they knew
we couldn't say anything.
because we were all complicit.
‐ How could you allow this.
Kameo?
‐ By the time we realized
what they were doing.
they'd shipped out
all the patients and staff.
But in the back of my mind.
I knew they sunk the ship.
When Hunter tied the boat
at the bottom of the ocean
to Revok.
there was no denying
what I had been a party to‐‐
what I had done.
‐ You're not seeing
the bigger play here.
The trials actually worked.
Those patients'
hideous reactions
were not side effects.
They were the desired effects.
‐ So they developed a drug
that would weaponize
an entire population?
One that would destroy itself
from within?
‐ A biological weapon
is worth more
on the black market
than any antiaging drug.
[dirt rustling]
[zombies snarling]
[gun clicks]
‐ Come on. Let's move.
‐ Go.
Go!
[tense music]
I got this. guys.
[sword crackles]
♪ ♪
Run!
Go!
Keep going!
♪ ♪
‐ [screeches]
[both panting]
‐ Come on.
[grunts]
[electricity crackles]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
‐ Daddy. come...
[sobs]
♪ ♪
‐ Wasp knife?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Got another?
‐ Have this one.
Don't you have enough
toys already?
‐ No.
‐ I love you.
‐ Grab the bag. Let's go.
‐ [groans]
♪ ♪
‐ Okay.
‐ All right.
Let's get to it.
Come on. Taani.
‐ I'll catch up.
♪ ♪
[grenade clicks]
‐ All right. call me
if you get into any trouble.
Driscoll. what about the ones
still up at your house?
‐ You didn't think I took
all the C4 with me. did you?
[remote beeps]
‐ Ray.
see you on the other side.
‐ You too. brother.
Hey. man.
is that stuff stable?
‐ Stable as I am.
[chuckles]
‐ Move out my way.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
‐ Oh!
‐ There it is.
♪ ♪
[lock clicks]
[door creaks]
All right. the fuses blew
when the lines went down.
I can make the downed
power lines active again.
I'm gonna use those tidal pools
to complete the circuit.
Then we'll reset the breaker.
Once we do that.
the power's gonna flow.
‐ We're gonna have to hurry.
‐ I'll get the lines
in the water. Stay here.
Don't hit that switch
until I tell you.
Got it?
‐ Yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[zombies snarling]
‐ Time to kick some ass.
♪ ♪
‐ All right. hit it!
[electricity crackling]
‐ Guys. we got to hurry.
They're getting close.
‐ I still don't understand
why I have to be the one
to secure the bombs
to the sunken ship.
‐ Because I have to drive
this thing away
before the detonator goes off.
That's your stuff. and I'm not
putting her in the water.
‐ Okay. fine.
I'll make sure the C4
locks on to the boat.
Up to you to do the rest.
‐ Ah‐‐
I got it.
‐ I don't know why I keep
saying "yes" to everybody.
I don't even like people.
‐ Maybe 'cause
you're kind of a good guy.
‐ Nope.
[power lines buzzing]
‐ Okay.
It worked.
‐ And now we got
to get the zombies.
‐ We need bait.
‐ Okay.
I'm gonna Pied Piper them
to follow me
into the tidal pools.
Once I do...
‐ We'll pull the switch.
‐ Exactly.
[energetic music
playing over boom box]
[bike revvs]
Hey!
Come and get it!
Come over here!
Come on!
Come and get me!
♪ ♪
Over here!
Hey!
Hey. over here!
‐ ♪ All dead.
not a bunch of dead beats ♪
♪ All dead.
it's gonna get... ♪
‐ Oh. yeah.
Come and get it.
Come on!
‐ ♪ So cue the operation ♪
♪ All dead.
dancing in damnation ♪
till the morning light ♪
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Oh ♪
♪ One of us ♪
♪ Oh ♪
‐ Throw me the C4 once I go in.
Time to fight crazy with crazy.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [snarling]
‐ Driscoll. get out the water!
Move!
[gun clicks]
Move. Driscoll!
Move!
‐ [snarls]
‐ [grunts]
‐ No!
No!
[flesh squelching]
‐ Go up front.
[energetic music
playing on boom box]
[tires rustling on dirt]
[engine revving]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
‐ [grunting]
‐ [deep howl]
‐ Hunter needs help.
‐ You stay here!
‐ Be careful!
[sword crackling]
‐ Come on.
Come on.
[crackle dies down]
♪ ♪
[bike revs]
[energetic music plays]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[electricity crackles]
Now!
Throw the switch!
‐ Okay.
[grunting]
♪ ♪
‐ Hurry.
They're close.
[gunshot]
‐ Put this vest on.
Get in the water.
[gun clicks]
‐ It's not happening.
[gunshot]
‐ Taani!
‐ No.
‐ No!
‐ Taani!
Look. when that anchor
hits the bottom.
this boat is not going anywhere.
‐ Your point?
‐ If your dad was here.
he'd kick my butt if
I didn't kick you off my boat.
so I'm kicking you off my boat!
‐ Okay.
‐ [grunts]
‐ When you get in the water.
hold the vest.
lay back. and ride the wave.
‐ [grunts]
‐ What about the zombies?
‐ Oh. don't worry about them.
They don't have a prayer.
♪ ♪
‐ [grunting]
It's not working!
♪ ♪
‐ Come on.
[sword crackles]
[zombies snarling]
‐ [grunts]
[electricity crackles steadily]
‐ Mom!
Mom! It worked.
‐ Hey. Hunter.
It's Ray. Come in.
[radio static]
Hunter?
Hunter. do you copy?
‐ Ray. we got them.
What's going on out there?
‐ It's a little rough out here.
but I'm about
to catch the big one.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[explosion]
‐ Oh. God.
‐ Come on. Hunter!
[dramatic musical sting]
‐ Oh. come on.
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
[soft dramatic music]
[dog whimpers]
♪ ♪
[tender music]
[clears throat]
‐ Oh. my...
‐ Hey.
‐ I didn't think you made it.
‐ [sighs] Looks like
we got most of them.
‐ [coughs]
‐ Mom.
Come on.
Taani?
I've got you.
‐ Help.
[both grunt]
‐ [coughs]
‐ Are you okay?
It's okay.
Sit down.
‐ What about Ray?
‐ You're gonna be okay.
A little bruised up.
but you just need rest.
♪ ♪
‐ Are you still leaving?
‐ Not on your life. Kenzie.
‐ Good.
'cause you still owe me dinner.
‐ And wine.
‐ And a movie.
‐ Anything else?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ It's about time.
‐ Finally.
‐ Come on.
What are we gonna do now?
‐ Whatever we do.
we're doing it together.
‐ [laughs softly]
♪ ♪
["Party (To Raise the Dead)"
acoustic version playing]
‐ ♪ You hear the sounds
that come in waves ♪
♪ ♪
♪ By people dancing
on a grave ♪
♪ And things are just about
to get depraved ♪
♪ We'll party. party ♪
♪ Party.
party to raise the dead ♪
♪ Party. party ♪
♪ Party to raise the dead ♪